cowboylyrics.com 2019-04-16

# Cowboy Lyrics. Privacy

|  |  |   
---|---  
  |  |  |   
  
**Country Lyrics and Tabs Source #1**

| **PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT FOR COWBOYLYRICS.COM**  
---  
  
CowboyLyrics.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: CowboyLyrics.com.

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

**Legitimate Interest**

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more det ails including opt \- out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com 

**Consent**

Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on o ur website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time via. For more details including access requests a nd complaints, review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com 

**Advertisers**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Read Amazon [privacy policy here](http://rcm.amazon.com/e/cm/privacy-policy.html?o=1).  
Read AllPosters [privacy policy here](http://www.allposters.com/help/guarantee.asp#privacy).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites. CowboyLyrics.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**

This site forum and guestbook available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Fair Use Notice**

This web site may contain copyrighted material whose use has not been   
specifically authorized by the copyright owner. This page is operated under the   
assumption that this not-for-profit use on the Web constitutes a "fair use"  
of the copyrighted material as provided for in Title 17, Chapter 1 , section 107 of the US Copyright Law. If you wish to use this copyrighted material for purposes of your own that go beyond "fair use", you must obtain permission from the copyright owner. 

**Copyright**

The copyright law of the United States (Title 17, U.S. Code) governs the making of photocopies or other reproductions of copyrighted material. Under certain conditions specified in the law, libraries and archives are authorized to furnish a photocopy   
or other reproduction. One of these specified conditions is that the photocopy or reproduction is not to be "used for any purpose other than private study, scholarship, or research." If a user makes a request for, or later uses, a photocopy or reproduction for purposes in excess of "fair use," that user may be liable for copyright infringement.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.  
  
 Advertising   

Site contains country lyrics, tablature/tab from any classic and popular song, compilation. Song text, lyric, guitar tabs/tablatures, basses, chords, notes, sheet music from many of country music styles Alt-Country & americana, folk, bluegrass, poetry, contemporary country, country gospel, cowboy songs, honky-tonk, outlaw & progressive country, traditional country, western swing. (country tabs, country tablatures for gutiar).   
  
|  |  | 

All lyrics are property and copyright of their owners. All lyrics provided for educational purposes only.  
  
---|---
